I don't know how I can put this because I don't
no sé cómo puedo poner esto porque no
have the application, let's see, I'm going to
tengo la aplicación a ver lo voy a
try to put it from my mobile, let's see, I
intentar poner desde el móvil a ver lo
'm going to try to put it from my mobile, I
voy a intentar poner desde el móvil o
mean, d made a song for Ricky
sea d le ha hecho una canción a Ricky
eddit
eddit
eh d made a song for Ricky
eh d le ha hecho una canción a Ricky
edit I
edit yo la
listened to it and mother of God I listened to it and
escuché y madre de Dios yo la escuché y
mother of God wait and see
madre de Dios espérate a ver siend
if it's just ricked Nando with his
si es simplemente ricked Nando de
back turned Ricky edit your meat sefla
espaldas Ricky edit tu carne sefla
when you have to
cuando tienes que
[Music]
[Música]
do what he said about pee have you
hacer qué ha dicho del pipí habéis
understood
entendido
[Music]
[Música]
that's
eso qué
disgusting mushroom factory what a
asco fábrica de hongos
stupid day with your entry into prison they're
mos diá tonto con tu ingreso en prisión
going to break your ass without asking your
te van a partir el culo sin pedirte tu
opinion they're going to break your ass without
opinión te van a partir el culo sin
asking your opinion Hi Javier in the end
pedirte tu opinión Hola Javier al final
what was wismichu's announcement Well, he hasn't
qué era el anuncio de wismichu Pues no
done anything I mean, yes, it's true that it had
ha hecho nada O sea sí que es verdad que
n't occurred to me as you can understand
no había caído como como entenderéis
we had something a little not a
hemos tenido algo un poco no un día un
little curious day and And yes, it's true that it hadn't
poco curioso y Y sí que es verdad que no
occurred to me that it was today today is
había caído en que era hoy hoy es
Friday No, but I understand that I do
viernes No pero entiendo que
n't understand that for whatever reason he won't
no entiendo que por lo que sea pues no
have seen that it's the right day  I don't
habrá visto que sea el día adecuado no
know what you can see, maybe there
sé a qué se puede ver a que a lo mejor
's an issue right now that
hay un tema ahora mismo en el que está
everyone's focused on and he prefers to
todo el mundo centrado y y prefiere
take a day when it's calmer
[__] un día que esté más tranquilito
to get more attention, I imagine. I don't
para tener más atención me imagino No lo
know, with mushrooms, hold
sé con hongos aguanta
the tupito, with mushrooms, he can't hold the
la tupito con hongos no aguanta la
expression, I mean, Gustavo Adolfo sees that er
expresión o sea Gustavo Adolfo ve que er
this eh Gustavo Adolfo sees that er that eh They'll
esto eh Gustavo Adolfo ve que er eso eh
put you in for your harassment and aggression
Te meter por tu acoso y agresión
[Music]
[Música]
Javi reacts Karina, I don't know what
Javi reacciona la Karina no sé que es la
Karina is, the problem is that there are
Karina es que el problema que hay
some things that I'm not
algunas cosas que no las estoy
understanding the words, I don't know if
entendiendo las palabras no sé si
you guys are or it's because of such
ustedes s o es por tal
[Music]
[Música]
nose and a dick that stinks
nariz de y un [__] que apesta
[ __ ] this song is better edited than
shit esta canción está mejor editada que
the previous one, man, it has its rhythm,
la anterior hombre tiene su ritmo no es
the lyrics are not a little disgusting but
un poco asquerosa la letra pero
[Music]
[Música]
Well, Andorra has your smell there
bueno andorra tien tu olor hay
and there are people who get kicked out because of the
y hay gente a la que le echan por la
stench of the penis,
peste del pene
no, but Rick What's wrong with Ricky, he's been really
no pero Rick Qué le pasa a Ricky está
quiet lately, where the [ __ ]
como mu callado últimamente dónde [__]
is he, [ __ ], I don't know, I have to upload the
está [__] no sé tengo que subir el
rewind, man, we have to do the rewind,
rewind tío tenemos que hacer el rewind
man, I think tonight  we're going to
tío creo que esta noche poco vamos a
sleep little what's up conchi today what do you want
dormir qué va conchi hoy qué quies
wizard that monetize the live
wizard que que se monetic el directo de
what Ah It's true wizard [ __ ] stop for
qué Ah Es verdad wizard [__] para una
once you're telling me something useful
vez que me estás diciendo algo útil
dude stop for once you're telling me
tío para una vez que me estás diciendo
something Useful it's true dude I wasn't
algo Útil es verdad tío no estaba
monetizing the live dude I wasn't
monetizando el directo tío ni estaba
monetizing the live nor was I [ __ ] You're welcome idiot
monetizando el directo ni estaba [__]
Suck my dick okay yes I'm
De nada [__] Chúpame la [__] vale si
going to put the monetization of the video
voy a poner la monetización del vídeo
but I'm going to tell you to suck my dick so you take
pero te voy a dec que me chupes la [__]
away the
para que me quites la
monetization you idiot not
monetización [__] ni
idiot I know dude he's telling me
[__] se tío me está diciendo todos
nonsense every day well for once he
los días tontería pues para una vez que
's telling me something true what's
me está diciendo algo de verdad que hace
necessary Well I don't pay [ __ ] attention to you Heavy
falta Pues no te hago [__] caso Pesado
Ah well then he'll tell her that that's
Ah bueno pues le dirá que eso es lo
normal that they condemn you for that but
normal que te condenen por eso pero
anyway I don't like to make
bueno de todas maneras a mí no me gusta
these predictions no I mean we don't
sacar estas predicciones no O sea no
know what can happen for example
sabemos lo que puede pasar por ejemplo
with your dor I was
con tu dor me
wrong with Lili let's see it could be
equivoqué con Lili a ver puede ser
true but with another lathe surely
verdad pero con otro torno seguramente
a little bit it's a little bit
un poquito está un poquito
[Music]
[Música]
8 am in Thailand But well conchi no, he
8 am en Tailandia Pero bueno conchi no
was telling me that today  we're not going to
que me estaba diciendo que hoy no vamos
sleep it's like 2 in the afternoon in
dormir es como a las 2 de la tarde de
Thailand then get with cheese late
Tailandia luego ponte con queso tarde
two or three hours too
dos o tres horas también
then we're talking about
entonces estamos hablando de
we're talking in 8 9 hours
las estamos hablando dentro de 8 9 horas
surely we're talking about 8 9
seguramente estamos hablando de 8 9
hours So yes I'm going to sleep
horas Entonces sí que voy a dormir
because I can't take it anymore I'm talking
porque ya no puedo más estoy hablando
to Paloma who just got up and I
con Paloma que se acaba de levantar y
'm talking a little with
estoy hablando un poco con
her and now when and now when
ella y ahora cuando y ahora cuando
the live ends I'm going to be here for a
termine el directo voy a estar aquí un
little while watching some things and we're going
ratito viendo algunas cosas y nos vamos
[Music]
[Música]
cl I raped you so much in the debate that they'll
cl te violé tanto en el debate que me
call me I raped you so much in the debate that they
llamarán te violé tanto en el debate que
call me what do you understand Put Paloma
me llaman qué lo entendéis Pon a Paloma
on call see how she is I don't think she wants to I do
en llamada ve cómo está no creo que
n't think she wants to
quiera no creo que quiera
eh I don't think she wants the
eh No creo que quiera la
truth Now when I Now when I
verdad Ahora cuando me Ahora cuando me
tell me something again she's
me vuelva a decir algo que está
advancing some things so I can go out
adelantando unas cosas para poder salir
Ah Town that they call it Town [ __ ] I
Ah Town que lo llaman Town hostias
raped you so much in the debate that they call me
te violé tanto en el debate que me
Town How have I If I hadn't
Town Cómo ha Si eso no me había dado
realized that I hadn't
cuenta No me había dado
realized I hadn't realized
cuenta No me había dado cuenta
lol lol
lol lol